[{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980298443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":41277,"timeElapsed":121862},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980310606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":12162,"timeElapsed":134026},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980326168,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":15560,"timeElapsed":149588},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980331778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":5609,"timeElapsed":155198},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980344168,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":12388,"timeElapsed":167588},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980349980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5811,"timeElapsed":173400},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980354495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4514,"timeElapsed":177915},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980365502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11005,"timeElapsed":188922},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980371580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6077,"timeElapsed":195000},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980409908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":35901,"timeElapsed":233328},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980412838,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2929,"timeElapsed":236258},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417948,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5109,"timeElapsed":241368},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427002,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":9053,"timeElapsed":250422},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2623,"timeElapsed":253046},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":4461,"timeElapsed":257508},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6429,"timeElapsed":263938},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5405,"timeElapsed":269344},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980455338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":9413,"timeElapsed":278758},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7991,"timeElapsed":286749},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980497752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":32403,"timeElapsed":321172},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6764,"timeElapsed":327937},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980509846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5327,"timeElapsed":333266},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980512907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3061,"timeElapsed":336327},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980517986,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5077,"timeElapsed":341406},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4226,"timeElapsed":345633},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3615,"timeElapsed":349249},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980530228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4397,"timeElapsed":353648},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980535478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5249,"timeElapsed":358898},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980538580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3101,"timeElapsed":361999},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7815,"timeElapsed":371898},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980551633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3155,"timeElapsed":375053},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5217,"timeElapsed":380272},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980559860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3007,"timeElapsed":383280},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980563868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4007,"timeElapsed":387288},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980571601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":7733,"timeElapsed":395021},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3381,"timeElapsed":398403},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980581827,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6843,"timeElapsed":405247},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980584679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2851,"timeElapsed":408099},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980597258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":10557,"timeElapsed":420678},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980601295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":4037,"timeElapsed":424715},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980608663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":7367,"timeElapsed":432083},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980612499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3835,"timeElapsed":435919},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980617483,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4983,"timeElapsed":440903},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980620803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3319,"timeElapsed":444223},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3576,"timeElapsed":447801},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980627927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3545,"timeElapsed":451347},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980630685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2757,"timeElapsed":454105},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":31061,"timeElapsed":487093},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3257,"timeElapsed":490351},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4773,"timeElapsed":495125},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2077,"timeElapsed":497203},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7193,"timeElapsed":504397},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4625,"timeElapsed":509023},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6599,"timeElapsed":515624},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980699023,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":6818,"timeElapsed":522443},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980702609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"183","question":"Who was your favorite teacher in school and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3585,"timeElapsed":526029},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":36849,"timeElapsed":564149},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980743315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2585,"timeElapsed":566735},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980748815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5499,"timeElapsed":572235},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980751673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2857,"timeElapsed":575093},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980759571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7897,"timeElapsed":582991},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980764321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4749,"timeElapsed":587741},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3648,"timeElapsed":591391},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980772775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":4803,"timeElapsed":596195},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1959,"timeElapsed":598155},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980782485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5939,"timeElapsed":605905},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980786633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4147,"timeElapsed":610053},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980794751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":8117,"timeElapsed":618171},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980797945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3193,"timeElapsed":621365},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980802822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4875,"timeElapsed":626241},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980806273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3450,"timeElapsed":629693},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980810015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3741,"timeElapsed":633435},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980817571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7555,"timeElapsed":640991},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980819593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2021,"timeElapsed":643013},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980839475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":18409,"timeElapsed":662895},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980842545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3069,"timeElapsed":665965},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980847569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":5023,"timeElapsed":670989},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980851568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":3998,"timeElapsed":674988},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980858085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6515,"timeElapsed":681505},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980862905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4819,"timeElapsed":686325},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980865943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3037,"timeElapsed":689363},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980875311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":9367,"timeElapsed":698731},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3951,"timeElapsed":702683},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980902971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":21789,"timeElapsed":726391},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980905713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2741,"timeElapsed":729133},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980910885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":5171,"timeElapsed":734305},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980913627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2741,"timeElapsed":737047},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980919073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5445,"timeElapsed":742493},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980923721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4647,"timeElapsed":747141},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980926721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2999,"timeElapsed":750141},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980933635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6913,"timeElapsed":757055},{"subjectID":"ugzu28vx55","prolificID":"5cc482bd8d2a1e001885c450","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2412a5378f6c7b540bc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980936275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2639,"timeElapsed":759695}]